{
    "id": "0e9b8b6a6b35461992a4c8786da4912e",
    "title": "Sentence Agreement Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The state of affairs .................................... sure to cause him anxiety.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e8150a64691d44ebb5296650e3678411"
        },
        {
            "question": "The introduction of reforms ...................................... not liked by the aristocracy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f1b49692bebd4ec784c1d956e50d0dd3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Bread and butter ................................... wholesome.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "813ad3d301634aeeacc92fc4fea633b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Slow and steady ....................................... the race.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "win",
                "wins"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "11ace2eb537e403e87d95e93ae66f933"
        },
        {
            "question": "Silver as well as gold ..................................... a precious metal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f6d50d58badb4a59a12e81fe2a6b81de"
        },
        {
            "question": "James together with his friends ....................................... present at the venue.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "de3f2768cc45421e9bc71e8d92a7995d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither the old man nor his sons ......................................... able to give a satisfactory explanation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3c9474240ea548228e065fcede1d0be9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither of the two plans ..................................... approved.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "85ba474c09e7489cb4866e20e4916bf9"
        },
        {
            "question": "The jury ...................................... divided in their opinions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "23c55a45456b4a428721c4311e88dd01"
        },
        {
            "question": "Thrice-told Tales ..................................... an interesting book.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f91ec657b43548faa489a41277e770d5"
        }
    ]
}